https://www.creativeuncut.com/privacy.html

CONTACT
CU's concept art library has 53,614 artworks from 961 games.
PRIVACY & ADVERTISING DISCLAIMER
This notice is provided for the purpose of helping you understand how your privacy is handled when visiting the CreativeUncut.com domain and all of its subdomains. It details the ways in which information may be collected and used, and explains what options you have to control those practices. This statement may be updated from time to time, and you are encouraged to regularly review it for any changes.
Amazon Associate Disclosure
Creative Uncut is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.
Information About Ad-Serving
This website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads to visitors. These companies may use information from visitors to this and other websites to provide advertisements about related goods and services. This information does not include your name, address, email address, or telephone number.
Cookies & Advertisers
A cookie is a data file stored on a user's computer that holds information about the user. Your browser should have user options for managing cookies, such as blocking all cookies, blocking cookies from specific sites, or controlling how long they are saved on your computer. These cookie options are usually found under a privacy tab in your browser options.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to
know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, then click here.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics to better understand visitors and develop better content. Google Analytics is a service that tracks and reports website traffic. It records non-personally identifiable information such as IP address, country, date & time of access, length of access, pages viewed, browser type, operating system, referring website, etc. If you wish to opt-out of Google Analytics tracking on all websites, Google provides a browser add-on that will disable the JavaScript for their tracking service.
GDPR & Privacy for EU Users
We work only with advertising companies who are GDPR compliant. Creative Uncut does not collect or store user data, use 3rd party plug-ins, offer membership areas, or make use of commenting platforms.
Fan Art Submissions
This website has, in the past, accepted fan artwork submitted by visitors. The artists had the option of providing a username of their choice along with their fan art to be posted on the Creative Uncut website. By default, an artist's email address and real name was not listed with their artwork unless explicitly requested.
If you have submitted fan art in the past and requested to include your name or email address but have since changed your mind, please contact me and I will promptly remove any information at your request.
Links
Creative Uncut contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy terms or content of such linked websites.
Changes to This Policy
At times, there may be changes made to this privacy policy to accommodate changes to the website and/or the handling of advertising. Whenever this occurs, the changes will be made to this page.
Questions or Concerns
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or the practices of this website, please feel free to contact us via the info page.
CU offers 5 ways to follow us so your news feed will never lack new art and inspiration. Get daily updates for video game art galleries packed with loads of concept art, character artwork, and promotional pictures.
WEBSITE INFO
© Creative Uncut 2003–2020
Privacy Policy & Amazon Disclaimer
About Us
Affiliated Sites & Links
